WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
You were right. Forensics has signed off
on him. The body can be released.
Why don't you wait
till they fix him up over there?
I promised our mother
I'd see him like we knew him, Jimmy,
before they put on all that pancake and shit.
Your funeral director's car is here.
I'll go down and meet them.
John, how long I gotta wait?
Tony Soprano left to his own device
is never gonna give up
that fuckin' animal Blundetto.
- Philly...
- An eye for an eye?
This is kinda fun.
But, if I was you, I'd dump this job.
I'd go to Italy.
This is no way for a caretaker to live.
Well, a few things have to settle down first.
My cousin'll send the funds
to go through Canada.
Italy. Wow. Nice cousin.
Oh, hey, thanks for that massage.
My toe doesn't hurt hardly at all now.
Watch the windows.
Excuse me.
How ya doing? You're Joanne, right?
- Who are you?
- Well, we're friends of your son's.
My son doesn't live with me.
We're... from Alcoholics Anonymous.
What's your name?
Well, we're anonymous.
I see his car's out front.
He went to California or Vegas, I don't know.
California or Vegas. When did he leave?
- I'm sorry, I have to go to work.
- Where the fuck is he?
- Leave me alone.
- I had a brother your son's age.
Please let go of my hand.
Where the fuck is he, you fuckin' cunt?
I'll take that Discman and I'll ram it up your box.
Philly, please!
It's the guy's mother, Phil.
It's the guy's mother.
Those jocks are juicers.
- They'll do it for the free brew.
- You're still here?
I'm driving to school,
I don't have to leave as early.
He'll bring some cool people.
- What are you doing up?
- Snowblower.
Seems to me you are not
sleeping that well, period.
Look at you.
I told AJ to fix this leak while
I was still at my mother's.
What's going on with him?
Every time I go by the room he's on the bed
on the phone.
I am so sick of nagging him.
And if he thinks he's gonna get into East
Stroudsburg State, he is sadly mistaken.
Look at this kid out there, the gardener's son.
- Can't ask this one to take out the trash.
- Poverty is a great motivator.
- You think we gave AJ too much?
- Then you look at Meadow.
Same house, everything. She's doing great.
She takes after you maybe.
Don't do that. He's my son too.
I got that appointment with his coach today.
Maybe he's got a clue.
- Hello?
- In here, Dad.
Hey, there's my little amaretto cookie.
Clear a place so we can take a look at these.
Only preliminary drawings.
I've got scones if anybody wants.
Take a look at the house
your mother's gonna build!
And Grandpa, of course.
Tony, Ignatz is responsible for those Normandy
chateaux up on Tisch Drive.
Wow, look at that entry. What is that,
like three storeys high?
- T?
- Christopher, hi, it's Carmela.
- Is Adriana there?
- No.
I was just wondering what was going on.
I stopped by Fortunoff's.
She was supposed to get back to them about
her china pattern
and she hasn't returned their calls.
Is everything all right?
- We broke up.
- What?
Why? What happened?
Nothing. She left. Broke my heart.
Moved out a couple of days ago,
I haven't seen her.
Oh, no, that's terrible. Are you all right?
She stiffed me on the club,
never showed up for work.
Oh, my God! Is there anything I can do?
Well, look, I gotta go.
- Somebody's waiting.
- I am devastated.
I want to reach her. Is there a number?
Not that I know of.
Chris, listen, there's other fish in the sea.
I know. Thanks.
Tony Soprano and Vito Spatafore
talking about the bus station project.
Adriana La Cerva. The way we make it
she's either taken off or maybe gotten clipped.
- You hear anything?
- Clipped, why?
- Stepping out on her boyfriend.
- I heard she took off.
- Any idea where?
- How should I know? He's a dope addict!
Did I already give you that?
- If you hear anything let me know.
- Say hello to lke and the guys.
T's held up. He said to start without him.
- All right?
- Yeah.
What can we say about this guy?
The ancient Romans had a word for it...
Asshole.
In all candour though, we love you, Raymond.
Take that away. He ain't coming.
- Who, Chris?
- South with the geese.
Christopher is the logical sacrifice bunt.
- The dead brother.
- I'm his brother-in-law.
Think New York is really gonna
come after you?
The fuck do I know?
If you're them, you want somebody
close to Tony as possible.
And who knows him better and longer?
Johnny's gonna
put a financial squeeze on all of us.
I'm already getting
fucked with by Johnny's people.
- It's not good.
- All due respect,
I'm willing to die for a good cause.
- But this is bullshit.
- There he is!
Sit down.
What's going on?
Vito misto, how are ya?
- Happy birthday, Ray.
- Thanks for coming, Tone.
I brought these plus... that's a good one.
I serve it at my house. It's from Avellino.
My grandfather said that some
of my ancestors were winemakers.
- What the fuck do I know?
- Thanks, Tone.
That's gonna be a treasure.
Yeah, well, whatever.
Larry!
What the fuck are you doing here?
- You're under house arrest.
- Fuck them.
I ever see that prison doctor, I'm gonna say,
"Did they ever show you these in medical
school? They're called balls."
Good for you!
Listen, I can't stay.
I got a meeting I gotta go to.
I got something I wanna say.
My cousin Anthony
went into business for himself.
We all know this.
In a way for which there is no excuse.
He's got a problem with rage.
He disappointed me, Anthony, in ways
that I can't even begin to tell you.
And he put us all at risk.
Irregardless,
it's been made clear to me
that if they put their hands on him,
he will not be dealt with quick.
We're talking torture.
For that reason, even if
I knew where my cousin was and I do not,
I would not deliver him up to them.
I am offering him the same protection
that I would offer any of you
in similar circumstances.
I know what you're gonna say.
"Hey, I would never do what he did."
God bless, I hope not. But we are a family.
And even in this fucked-up day
and age that means something.
So we are gonna deal
with this as a family, together.
No matter how it affects anybody
personal safety-wise,
financially-wise, whatever.
I see that my nephew isn't here
and it's important he lam it now.
It's my desire that you circle
the wagons, you support him.
Until and as such...
Raymond. I'm sorry I can't stay.
Happy birthday, huh?
- Thanks.
- Gentlemen, enjoy your dinner.
See ya, T.
Thank you. That was great.
- Thought you had Raymond's birthday dinner.
- I left early.
It's nice you're home.
There's chicken parm.
Was Christopher there?
No.
Did you know that him and Adriana broke up?
This kid, that's his trouble.
He keeps it all bottled up.
Then they wonder why they
get chemical dependencies.
Do you think there was somebody else?
There was this one night, it was way back,
movie night with the girls.
Adriana was upset and wanted to get
something off her chest.
Then she ran out crying.
I'll bet she was seeing somebody.
You never know about people.
His plans were often startling,
instinctive, spontaneous,
and not infrequently, obscure.
His men idolised him
and had boundless faith in him.
After being promoted in 1916,
he joyfully returned home on leave
to marry his sweetheart, Lucie Maria Mollin.
She would be the love of his life to its end.
Rommel saw the huge assault on France
forming,
and he saw that a new armoured weapon...
I still love this old house so much.
I should do half so good with my stupid project.
...almost precisely what he had done
as a lieutenant during WWI.
I'm sorry, did you wanna be alone?
No.
...blitzkrieg in its truest form.
It was Rommel...
He had what the Germans call
Fingerspitzengefühl,
which is a sixth sense of sizing up a
situation.
- Claude Rains.
- Thanks for doing this.
About 1500 there. Should tide you over.
- Hey, Sil.
- Hey, kid.
You want something? Fries?
- It's fuckin' something, this situation.
- Right.
I can't even get down
to Milt's, fence some jewellery.
Everybody with eyes in the back of their head.
- I was Tony's driver.
- It's amazing.
You want me to be honest?
The favouritism Tony still shows for our fuckin'
cousin, after what he's done?
What does Tony B have on this guy?
I might take a bullet for this skeeve.
After all your uncle's done for you?
I need to get into specifics?
You said you went home.
Just heard her old man died. I'll give her a call.
Actually, I've been hanging around on purpose.
I gotta talk to you, Tone.
About what?
- I've been your consigliere for years.
- Don't go into a fuckin' preamble.
- Tell me what's on your mind.
- You got some unhappy people out there.
- No shit.
- Not just the young guys.
Guys that've been
with you since the beginning.
Before the beginning.
Guys who worked for your father.
- Fuckin' Paulie, right?
- I'm not saying nothing.
Goddamn him.
These guys, would do whatever you ordered.
- Except in this case.
- Don't say it like that.
Forget that Tony Blundetto's my cousin.
I give him up, we can give
the whole fuckin' thing up.
Here's where the conversation gets difficult.
- Go.
- All due respect.
You were ready to hand him your cousin
a week ago.
It's not about standing with the guys
or upholding some rules. Not really.
Then what's it all about?
Why don't you illuminate me?
It's about you don't wanna eat shit from John.
You don't wanna bow down.
You told him to go fuck himself.
Which, to be honest,
wasn't exactly appropriate, considering.
- Oh, is that right?
- All due respect.
What the fuck do you know
what goes on in my head?
I've known you since you were a kid.
Frankly, you got a problem with authority.
This attitude of yours,
it's a lot of what's made you an effective leader.
But we all got flaws. Even you.
Seven deadly sins and yours is pride.
All due respect. You got no fuckin' idea
what it's like to be number one.
Every decision you make affects every facet of
every other fuckin' thing.
It's too much to deal with almost.
And in the end,
you're completely alone with it all.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
This is the course I've chosen,
and those of you that are not with me on it,
well, that makes me sad.
And it'll be dealt with in time.
You need me for anything else?
- Benny, right?
- How ya doing, Mr Leotardo?
I'm sitting listening to WFAN and I go,
isn't that the kid that used to drive for Tony?
- I'm on my way to the hospital.
- Well, that's up to you.
No, I mean my mom, she...
- Where's his friend?
- What friend?
Don't fuck with me, kid!
Don't fuck with me!
- Where's Blundetto?
- I don't know!
It's a start.
- Jesus.
- He has a fractured skull.
- Is he talking at all?
- A little.
Listen, Ben, I want you to know that...
...it'll be taken care of through
the plumber's union health plan.
You know what? We were talking here.
It's time for you to get your own customers.
You're getting a little too old
to be beating people up.
- Where's Larry?
- He's staying home.
He's the boy's godfather. He called me.
- Said he was gonna be with the kid.
- House arrest.
All right.
- This is fucked up.
- What do ya wanna do about it?
What do I wanna do? I want that man there
to do something about it.
I want him to give us the OK
to go to Brooklyn,
clean some timepieces over there.
Tony Blundetto whacked
the brother of a captain.
If Tony tried to strike at them again,
we should take him out.
Look, just give me that first one,
the Oregonian.
$39.95.
You're sending a fruit basket to the kid.
- He'll appreciate it.
- It's for Mel.
The poor guy had a stroke.
- He's younger than me.
- Melvoin?
Jesus Christ, that's terrible.
That's why I asked you to come over.
His speech...
He'll sound a little suonato,
probably forever.
But get this, nine months, maybe a year,
till he can work a full schedule.
They'll have to postpone my retrial.
No shit?
The question is, should I use the stall,
but then get a lawyer who's more with it?
You heard about this thing with Phil and John?
- Bobby said something about this.
- That you're losing money, probably.
- I am? How much?
- I don't know, you gotta talk to him.
Does John do your collections?
Look, Uncle Jun', what do you think?
Phil beat one of my guys
to within an inch of his life.
Next time he'll kill somebody.
What can I do? It's my cousin.
Did I give them
the office address or the home?
- I'm talking to you.
- He had a stroke.
You want it to go to the wrong place?
It's fruit, it'll rot.
I pinned myself into a corner here,
and I don't see a way out.
But he wasn't made, right?
The kid... Phil's son.
It's OK, forget it.
I'm sorry.
I'm fuckin' nonplussed with all this news.
Frankly, I don't know.
You're going a little squirrelly in this house.
- Tell Phil.
- Tell Phil what?
Where you going?
- You wanted to confer with me?
- Nah, it's not important.
Make sure you eat a lunch today.
Poor fuckin' Feech La Manna.
Tony sent the wrong ex-con back to jail.
You realise I had an entire container of
imported provolone coming in Saturday?
And fuckin' Phil and them put it on a truck,
took it to Westchester instead of Rahway
where we always split the loads.
Jesus. That shit is liquid gold.
Tony knows what has to be done.
Tell John where to find Blundetto.
He just won't do it.
As if he even knows where Tony B is.
Give me a fuckin' break. Of course he knows.
- It's Christopher I feel for.
- Please!
Let me tell ya something.
Soprano is very adroit
at keeping his family outta the frying pan.
Both cousins. The rest of us...
How's life now that you're back home?
I had a dream a couple of weeks ago.
Before I moved back, a recurring dream.
I see my old coach from high school.
What happens?
He told me back then, this guy, he said...
- he said that I was special.
- You never told me this.
Why now?
Does everything
I drag in here gotta be a dead dog?
I went to see my son's football coach.
See, he was starting my boy and now...
the coach is going to this other kid more.
What's the reason?
Well, AJ's just devoting
more energy to academics.
He's determined to get into a good school.
How's things on other fronts?
Your cousin?
Well, you touched
on something there that's not so good.
- What's the problem?
- I really can't talk to you about it.
This is very difficult for me, treating you,
when so much of your life is closed off.
How many times can I say this?
Look, I'm not trying to be difficult here.
It's just that it affects me tremendously,
this trouble he's gotten himself into,
so I'm upset!
Well...
- And I care about him so much.
- You care about him so much?
We spent hours getting to the realisation
that your feelings for your cousin stem
from guilt and shame.
Do you remember that? Do you care?
It's just that it doesn't matter now...
It's just that here we are, as always,
back at square one,
with you going into high-sentimentality mode.
Sentimentality mode?
We were children together!
Look, it's a lot like with your son.
Here's what I bet the coach didn't tell you.
What you wanted to hear most
is that your son is special too.
What I'm saying is, whatever you wanna do,
vis-à-vis your cousin, your son, whoever,
own your feelings!
- I'm very confused.
- But... we can't talk about it.
It's my mess.
All my choices were wrong.
- How much?
- It's five bucks.
Your cup's your admission pass.
- Where are they from?
- Montville.
They gotta go.
Totally.
- Hello?
- Chiara!
No, you gotta come up Greenbrook Road.
Patrick said to tell you some people have
bogus cups.
They brought them with them
to get out of paying.
- Hey, man, let me see your cup.
- It's in the Athletic Department.
We're getting ripped off.
This isn't downloading music.
That beer is our property unless you pay for it.
Fucking manners!
Speak.
Hello.
- Who is it?
- Open this door!
I wanna talk to you.
I hear you got some beefs.
Do you wanna phone everybody?
What the fuck?
I know you said you wanted it burnt, T,
but the picture moved me.
Cos you knew it cost me an arm and a leg.
It's museum-quality work, I admit that.
But I told the guys a chance to hang
a picture of you on my wall?
I rescued it from the flames.
What's with the hat and shit?
Don't give me "huh".
You know what it does to me?
- To be reminded of that fuckin' horse?
- I'm sorry, T.
But you never come here no more.
I didn't figure there'd be a problem.
I never come here no more
cos they're watching all our houses.
- It's no good for us to visit.
- I know.
Do you and your whores get a big laugh?
- That's no joke.
- Then what is it?
That's no joke! That cost me a lotta
money to get the retouching done.
What the fuck did you do it for?
And don't bullshit me, Paulie.
Part of it was to fix some fire damage
on the guy's feet.
But while I was at it, I also thought,
I don't have a modern look in here,
so go with something more traditional,
that catches more of what you're all about.
- A goddamn lawn jockey?
- That's not a lawn jockey.
That's a general.
What general? Who?
It's not a real general from history, it's you.
What the fuck.
Speak.
He's at 146, Route 9A, Kinderhook.
- Skip.
- How's it going?
We got you your bialys and coffee.
Johnny Sack called for you.
Called a couple of times.
He seemed upset about something.
- Good bialy.
- Any time, boss.
Catch ya later.
Take it easy, Tone.
- What?
- It didn't solve a thing.
- It's over, John.
- The fuck it is!
- He's beside himself now.
- The best thing for him,
for you, for all of us, is to put this thing behind
us and get back to business.
- How is that supposed to happen?
- It's something we gotta talk about.
As a first step, I'd consider giving Phil
a quarter of my points in the Bloomfield
operation, which my cousin was running.
I'm at Columbia Pres all day,
my yearly physical.
An hour already, I'm waiting for this doctor.
Then I got bone density tests, lipids.
Come into the city tonight.
No offence, John, but I got
an IQ of 136. It's been tested.
All right. Tomorrow morning then,
my house, 6:30.
- What?
- I'm on a 9.00 a.m. flight to Miami.
I have to get things in line there.
You think I'm gonna give you
ammazzo with Ginny upstairs?
- If you don't hear from me, I'll be there.
- Tony, you and you alone.
I'm not having Phil, nobody.
- Who is it?
- It's me.
You need to go up to the farm
and pick up your cousin.
I need you to go up there now, this morning.
It may be over, but watch your back.
Take him off the premises, obviously.
He should be buried.
It should be you that does it.
You got it.
We never got
a chance to talk in detail about Adriana.
I know.
If you let something slip,
if she saw anything...
There was a couple of times
I had her with me picking up collections.
Esplanade.
The cigarettes...
she was always nosing around.
Did you ever say anything
about Ralph or the Bevelaqua kid?
- No.
- Would you remember?
I swear on my life.
- You won't find any of that.
- I'm reading, I'm lifting weights.
I know what you think but you'll see.
I'm gonna prove myself to you.
I only chipped that once, on the day with her.
She was willing to rat me out
because she couldn't do five fuckin' years?
- I thought she loved me.
- She's a cunt.
Does no good to think about that now.
All right.
He does like her.
Cos he told me.
- I have heard you talking all night.
- Could you knock?
You said you'd finish your application.
You're gonna stroke out if you
can't find a way to control yourself.
- I know.
- Hang that phone up.
Call me back later?
I don't know what to say, you know?
If applications are late,
you are cooked. It's that simple.
I know this because I have
raised you from day one,
you won't like working at McDonald's.
- Could you up the drama a little?
- You know what?
I don't like the sarcasm,
and I don't want you around here
next year sponging off of us, so fine.
No allowance
until those applications are done.
That's not even practical and you know it.
- What's the matter?
- He hasn't done his applications.
- He isn't getting allowance.
- No allowance.
- I have $300 of my own money.
- How?
Me and Matt put on a party.
$5 a person. We made 600 bucks
after expenses.
- What expenses?
- The band.
Is that why you've been on the phone
for two weeks?
It may interest you to know
people said it was the best party all year.
- There was drinking?
- We just let people into Matt's house.
What they brought with them
was not under our control.
Do your applications. Now.
- What?
- You know, it's interesting.
I was talking to his college advisor...
Who, Wegler?
No, AJ got switched around. Miss Merrow.
She mentioned that AJ talked to her once
about what might be good schools
to study event planning.
Event planning?
What the hell is it?
I am not really sure.
- Gay, isn't it?
- I don't know.
I know you're around a lot of wealthy people.
He watches that DVD over and over again.
The one with Mike Myers about...
What's his name?
- Steve Rubell, the Studio 54 guy?
- Oh, Jesus.
Yeah, but I mean, you know, it...
Well, I guess, you know...
I don't know.
He's fired up about something at least.
So? Go ahead.
Phil has to know that punishment has been
meted out and that's all there is.
And that what we are here for, in the end,
is to put food on the table for our families,
our sons, the future.
- That's what's important.
- He doesn't accept that.
His family's smaller by one.
Well, then, my friend,
it's up to you to make him accept it.
- Me?
- Let's talk, John,
about the 500-pound elephant in the room.
You started this cycle of bloodshed when you
whacked the girl Carmine used to fuck.
Lorraine Calluzzo was not a girl,
and what kind of a man
bangs his second cousin?
What are you, the frigging cardinal?
You wanna shut down
our joint construction jobs?
Eat K-rations? Fine. You want Phil
to put one in one of my guys?
That's gonna go a long way to making you
the rich prick that you want to be.
- What do you suggest?
- Whatever his legitimate sorrow,
he's got a price.
He wants to provide for his family.
- And?
- And what?
Meet his price, and that's it.
- I don't wanna hear nothing else.
- Oh, you don't?
I've paid enough, John. I've paid a lot.
Maybe I could sell it.
Truth is we've had discussions.
I gave him the sports book.
Why didn't you say that, you cheap fuck?
Cos I don't like it.
He's gonna want consigliere or...
Let's not go backwards now.
These people you run into
who wanna be boss, huh?
- They should know.
- I told you. You don't listen, you nut.
It's good... seeing you again.
I still look forward
to working with you, John. I mean that.
- You want a coffee?
- Oh, I don't know.
Fuckin' Christ!
FBI, open up!
Oh, my God!
I'm the gardener.
Absolutely, put him on.
The Feds just hit Johnny Sack.
You heard anything?
I had Gendler on my cell phone
all the way over here.
Jimmy Petrille was a collaborator.
They took down
the whole Petrille crew plus Johnny.
Would've reached Carmine Senior
if he hadn't died.
Jimmy Petrille? He's a sweet old guy.
He gave them gambling,
homicides, trafficking...
18 fuckin' years' worth.
It's a major kreplach, my friend.
- I was fuckin' there.
- What, where?
Johnny's house. My car's in the driveway.
I'm walking three miles towards my house.
No law against parking your car
unless it's in front of a hydrant.
- I'm not laughing, Neil.
- No, of course not.
Anyway, you weren't named
in the indictment, obviously.
It's Brooklyn. They weren't coming for you.
So frankly, were I you,
I might actually consider laughing.
Or rub a hunchback's hump. Or something.
- Yeah.
- Be of good cheer.
Call you when I hear more.
What happened to you?
And your shoes are soaking wet.
English